

Sebastien Decuyper

Game Programmer

• Tempelhofer Weg 94, Berlin, Germany, 12347, Germany

± 14.07.1994

seb.decuyper@gmail.com

+33635404256

https://sebdec.net/

⇔ GlaasGD

in Sebastien Decuyper

SKILLS

C# Unity3D

Tool dev (C#, LUA, Python) Git

.NET VR/AR

Rust HTML/CSS/JS

INTERESTS

Creative coding (Shaders and virtual consoles) Blacksmithing

TTRPG

LANGUAGES

EnglishFluent

French

German

Beginner

PUBLICATIONS

Procedural Generation by Semantic Inference

04.08.2

ResearchGate

https://www.researchgate.net/pu blication/372904546_PROCEDURAL _GENERATION_BY_SEMANTIC_INFE RENCE Experienced Game Programmer with a passion for tech and a track record of three years in the industry. Contributed to the successful development of two shipped game titles while also building a diverse portfolio through extensive freelancing projects. A passion for developing tools and libraries. Started in game programming and progressively expanded expertise into broader areas of software development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wolpertinger Games

(01.09.2022 - Present)

Game Programer

Gameplay programing, Tool development, CI/CD, SDK Implementation (Steam, Twitch, Switch)

https://wolpertingergames.com/

smpl games

(01.06.2022 - 01.09.2022)

Game Programer

Android port, IAP implementation, Save system, Networking code, Gameplay programing

https://smpl.com/

Relative

(04.03.2022 - 15.12.2022)

VR / AR Programer

VR UI and interactions, Procedural Animations, Shader writing, Building and deployment, Project Management

https://relative.berlin/

University of Applied Sciences Europe

(02.05.2021 - 01.09.2022)

Studentische Hilfskraft

Tutoring, IT support, Project Management, Creation and updating of code libraries

https://www.ue-germany.com/

EDUCATION

University of Europe for Applied Sciences

(01.09.2020 - 14.07.2023)

Bachelor Game Design, Arts & Design

https://www.ue-germany.com/

Université Lumière Lyon 2 (01.09.2015 - 04.07.2018)

Bachelor Modern Literature

https://welcome.univ-lyon2.fr/

Ecole La Mache (04.09.2013 - 06.07.2015)

Bac Professionnel OMB - Ouvrage du bâtiment Métallerie

https://www.ecolelamache.org/

Lycée Georges Guynemer

(01.09.2011 - 14.06.2013)

CAP Ferronnerie d'Art (Blacksmithing)

https://guynemer.mon-ent-occitanie.fr/

REFERENCES

Sebastian Bender

CEO

**** +491743075656

s.bender@wolpertingergames.com

Florian Grolig

CEO

fgrolig@gmail.com

Florian Berger

Department Head

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

Devcom (24.08.2021 - 28.08.2021)

https://www.devcom.global/

A MAZE! Festival (15.05.2022 - 22.05.2022)

https://2023.amaze-berlin.de/

GamesweekBerlin (05.09.2022 - 22.09.2022)

https://www.gamesweekberlin.com/de/